themusicdynasty.com 2009-12-18

# Privacy Policy - The Music Dynasty | The Internet's #1 Music Forum

Welcome to The Music Dynasty, a hip hop, rap, and music discussion forum where you can join thousands of fans from all over the world discussing all things related to rap music and hip hop culture among other music. To gain full access to Music Dynasty you must **register for a free account and make a introduction post**. As a registered member you will be able to do the following.   

  * Participate in various forums and browse from over **1,000,000 posts**.
  * Download all the newest and hottest **[albums](http://www.themusicdynasty.com/forums/new-albums-2009/)** , **[mixtapes](http://www.themusicdynasty.com/forums/mixtapes-osts/)** , **[singles](http://www.themusicdynasty.com/forums/singles-chamber/)** , and **[videos](http://www.themusicdynasty.com/forums/multi-plex-chamber/)**. 
  * Show off your talents such as your producing skills, remixes, blends, etc. 

All this and much more is available to you absolutely free when you [**register**](http://themusicdynasty.com/forums/register.php) for an account, so [**sign up now**](http://themusicdynasty.com/forums/register.php)! 

If you have any problems with the registration process or your account login, please 

[**contact**](http://www.themusicdynasty.com/forums/sendmessage.php) the Music Dynasty Support Team. 

| The Music Dynasty's Privacy Policy  
---  
  
  * The Music Dynasty recognizes that you care about the personal information that is held about you and how that is used.

  * This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the The Music Dynasty web site.

  * By registering to The Music Dynasty you need to submit a chosen name and contact information, more specifically an e-mail address. No extremely personal information, such as Social Security or Credit Card numbers are stored by us.

  * The Music Dynasty also stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the webserver, and any trusted 3rd party we chose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. In general, cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from 'trusted' internet sites, such as The Music Dynasty. For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)

  * The Music Dynasty will not sell, transmit or distribute any data held without your prior permission or consent, unless required to do so under relevant United States legislation.

  * All other information provided by you goes into a "public profile" and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your Control Panel in the forums.

  * You have a legal right for the personal information held at The Music Dynasty to be updated if it is incorrect or deleted if you choose. Most of this can be done through your Control Panel in the forums. Please contact us for help regarding any issues with this.

  * The Music Dynasty will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is maintained secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.

  * This site is intended for individuals over the age of 13. Any information collected is intended to be of individuals over the age of 13. According to [COPPA](http://www.ftc.gov/coppa/index.html), our site does NOT cater to children. "Operators of commercial websites or online services directed to children under 13 that collect personal information from children" require a COPPA agreement and privacy policy. No COPPA exists on The Music Dynasty since we do not cater to this age group.

  * This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page for updates or changes. Please Contact Us if you have any questions regarding your privacy.

Powered by vBulletin® Version 3.8.4  
Copyright ©2000 - 2009, Jelsoft Enterprises Ltd. 

Search Engine Optimization by vBSEO 3.2.0

vBulletin Skin developed by: [1uxkz](http://www.themusicdynasty.com/forums/members/-1uxkz-.html)
